<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>TWC Showcase</title>
 <link href="http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase"/>
 <updated>2013-11-16T02:52:06-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase</id>
 <author>
   <name>Kyle Kinnaman</name>
   <email>kyle.kinnaman@ksuwdc.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Nissan - Pathfinder</title>
   <link href="http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/16/Nissan-Pathfinder"/>
   <updated>2013-11-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/16/Nissan-Pathfinder</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;26 MPG&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The legendary Pathfinder: rugged, capable, tough. And good on gas. To maximize fuel efficiency, the frame, drivetrain, and even the climate control system are built with lightweight components. An aerodynamic exterior and the Xtronic CVT® — our most advanced transmission ever — also cut down its consumption. All this adds up to 26 MPG on the highway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Hybrid System&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2.5-liter 4-cylinder engine is supercharged—meaning that there's 250 hp generated by Pathfinder's Hybrid system. The 15 kW power-regenerating electric motor is powered by lithium-ion cells, and the Intelligent Dual Clutch System efficiently manages power from both the electric motor and the engine. To save power, the gas engine only kicks in when it needs to, and switches to the electric motor to conserve fuel when you start-up, coast, or stop.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Panera - You've got the power</title>
   <link href="http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/14/Panera-Youve-got-the-power"/>
   <updated>2013-11-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/14/Panera-Youve-got-the-power</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Start your day with a mouthful of whole grain, all-natural egg, lean ham and tangy Vermont white cheddar, for real get up and go.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Bank of America - Homeowners</title>
   <link href="http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/14/Bank-of-America-Homeowners"/>
   <updated>2013-11-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.twcmediakit.com/showcase/2013/11/14/Bank-of-America-Homeowners</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you're a homeowner struggling with your loan payments, you may want to learn about our home loan assistance programs. Bank of America is committed to helping homeowners and is a participant in the national mortgage settlement agreement.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>